<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Olivia Sculley</title>
    <link>https://olivia.sculley.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Olivia Sculley</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 7 Jan 2024 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://olivia.sculley.dev/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Remember to feed your ZFS array</title>
      <link>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/feed-your-zfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/feed-your-zfs/</guid>
      <description>So, I&amp;rsquo;ve talked about my project server in the past, but I wanted to
        give a bit of an update after upgrading my server a bit. I go over more details in the
        previous post, but basically I had been running over 100 docker containers of various
        personal services with only 32 gigs of ram, which resulted in a bit of swap usage and no
        excess available ram, until now!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Server</title>
      <link>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/code-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/code-server/</guid>
      <description>So, imagine if there was a portable, convenient way to do software development
        from any of your web-capable devices, but also leverage the power of beefier machines to
        compile and run heavier applications? What if this coding environment was reproducible and
        allowed you to seemlessly switch between different devices or operating systems and pick up
        right where you left off?
        If you guessed it, this coding environment already exists from code-server, which lets you
        run VS Code on a remote server, accessible through the browser!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-hosted</title>
      <link>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/hosted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/hosted/</guid>
      <description>I feel like a home server is a bit like the techie&amp;rsquo;s project car. It
        might not work perfectly 100% of the time, and it might be a bit louder and take up more
        space in your garage, closet, or living room (if you&amp;rsquo;re like me) than your
        significant other might hope, but there&amp;rsquo;s nothing more rewarding than getting to
        take it out for a spin at the end of the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Software Hall of Fame</title>
      <link>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/free-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://olivia.sculley.dev/#/posts/free-software/</guid>
      <description>As you might know, I&amp;rsquo;m an avid free software advocate, and I try to use
        free software over proprietary ones as much as I reasonably can. These are some of the free
        software projects that I have found, which I either use on a daily basis or have made me say
        &amp;ldquo;how did I possibly live before this?&amp;rdquo;. Hopefully you&amp;rsquo;ll be
        able to discover a project that&amp;rsquo;ll make you feel the same, too!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
